Guide to the Charles and Shirley Weiss Collection of Opera Ephemera, 1951-2003 RL.11139
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Hippolytus and Aricia (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2001 June 22 (Box 2)
- Hydrogen Jukebox (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1990 May 29 (Box 2)
- I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky (Cal Performances, San Francisco, CA), 1995 May 17 (Box 2)
- Idomeneo (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 October 30 (Box 2)
- Idomeneo (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1985 June 22 (Box 2)
- Idomeneo (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 February 3 (Box 2)
- Idomeneo (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1994 January 8 (Box 2)
- Idomeneo (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1997 November 10 (Box 2)
- Idomeneo (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1999 August 5 (Box 2)
- Idomeneo (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1999 December 5 (Box 2)
- Idomeneo (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 October 18 (Box 2)
- The Impresario (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1989 January 29 (Box 2)
- The Impresario (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1993 June 13 (Box 2)
- Improvement (Site Santa Fe, Santa Fe, NM), 1995 August 3 (Box 2)
- The Inca's Chosen Bride (?, Chapel Hill, NC), 1997 September 12 (Box 2)
- L'Infedelta Delusa (Drottningholms Slottsteater, Stockholm, Sweden), 1963 August 20 (Box 2)
- The Informer (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1987 February 12 (Box 2)
- Intermezzo (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1994 July 23 (Box 2)
- Intimate Immensity (Center for Contemporary Arts, Santa Fe, NM), 1997 July 29 (Box 2)
- Iolanthe (Durham Savoyards, Ltd., Durham, NC), 1976 April 23 (Box 2)
- Iphigenie en Tauride (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1994 June 25 (Box 2)
- Iphigenie en Tauride (Glimmerglass Opera, Cooperstown, NY), 1997 August 23 (Box 2)
- Iphigenie en Tauride (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1997 October 9 (Box 2)
- Iphigenie en Tauride (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 2000 May 30 (Box 2)
- L'Italiana in Algeri (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 January 30 (Box 2)
- L'Italiana in Algeri (Teatro alla Scala, Milan, Italy), 1983 December 27 (Box 2)
- L'Italiana in Algeri (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1985 January 26 (Box 2)
- L'Italiana in Algeri (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 January 11 (Box 2)
- L'Italiana in Algeri (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1988 January 2 (Box 2)
- L'Italiana in Algeri (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1997 February 16 (Box 2)
- L'Italiana in Algeri (Glimmerglass Opera, Cooperstown, NY), 1997 August 23 (Box 2)
- L'Italiana in Algeri (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2002 August 3 (Box 2)
- L'Ivrogne Corrige (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1981 May 23 (Box 2)
- Jackie O (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1997 March 16 (Box 2)
- Die Jakobsleiter (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1980 August 7 (Box 2)
- Jenufa (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 October 5 (Box 2)
- Jenufa (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1986 September 19 (Box 2)
- Jenufa (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1992 January 14 (Box 2)
- Jenufa (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1998 May 22 (Box 2)
- Jenufa (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 2000 December 4 (Box 2)
- Jenufa (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2001 December 1 (Box 2)
- Joruri (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1985 June 25 (Box 2)
- The Journey to Rheims (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1986 June 20 (Box 2)
- Juana, La Loca (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1984 June 1 (Box 2)
- La Juive (Opera Orchestra of New York, New York, NY), 1999 April 13 (Box 2)
- Der Kaiser von Atlantis (Miller Theatre, New York, NY), 1998 September 18 (Box 2)
- Katya Kabanova (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1991 March 23 (Box 2)
- Katya Kabanova (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1995 January 17 (Box 2)
- Katya Kabanova (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1998 June 20 (Box 2)
- Katya Kabanova (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 2000 October 27 (Box 2)
- Katya Kabanova (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2002 November 20 (Box 2)
- Khovanshchina (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1984 November 24 (Box 2)
- Khovanshchina (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 November 9 (Box 2)
- Khovanshchina (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1988 March 12 (Box 2)
- King Arthur (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1989 June 24 (Box 2)
- King Arthur (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1991 January 27 (Box 2)
- The King Goes Forth to France (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1986 August 8 (Box 2)
- King of the Clouds (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1996 April 22 (Box 2)
- Kinkakuji (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1995 October 24 (Box 2)
- Kitty Hawk (National Opera Company, ?), 2000 April 25 (Box 2)
- Lady Kate (The Ohio Light Opera, Wooster, OH), 1994 June 8 (Box 2)
- Lady Kate (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1995 January 20 (Box 2)
- Lady Macbeth of Mtsensk (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1981 September 9 (Box 2)
- Lady Macbeth of Mtsensk (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1982 May 26 (Box 2)
- Lady Macbeth of Mtsensk (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1994 November 10 (Box 2)
- Lady Macbeth of Mtsensk (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2000 March 25 (Box 2)
- Lakme (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1983 October 8 (Box 2)
- Lakme (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1994 September 27 (Box 2)
- The Last Savage (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1981 May 22 (Box 2)
- Lear (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1981 June 23 (Box 2)
- Die Liebe der Danae (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1982 August 14 (Box 2)
- Die Liebe der Danae (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1985 August 2 (Box 2)
- Lilith (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2001 November 15 (Box 2)
- A Little Night Music (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1999 February 9 (Box 2)
- Little Women (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1998 March 12 (Box 2)
- Livietta e Tracollo (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1984 June 3 (Box 2)
- Lizzie Borden (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1999 March 24 (Box 2)
- Lohengrin (Opera de Hanovre, Lausanne, Switzerland), 1980 June 6 (Box 2)
- Lohengrin (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1980 October 31 (Box 2)
- Lohengrin (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 February 16 (Box 2)
- Lohengrin (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 January 4 (Box 2)
- Lohengrin (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1989 December 8 (Box 2)
- Lohengrin (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1994 August 10 (Box 2)
- Lohengrin (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1998 March 13 (Box 2)
- I Lombardi alla Prima Crociata (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1979 June 30 (Box 2)
- I Lombardi alla Prima Crociata (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1982 April 11 (Box 2)
- I Lombardi alla Prima Crociata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1994 January 15 (Box 2)
- Lord Byron's Lover Letter (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1986 May 30 (Box 2)
- Loss of Eden (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2002 June 20 (Box 2)
- Lost Eden (Arts in Duke Chapel, Durham, NC), 1982 November 8 (Box 2)
- Louise (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1999 September 22 (Box 2)
- The Love for Three Oranges (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1981 April 18 (Box 2)
- The Love for Three Oranges (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2000 November 5 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (Theatre Nationale Opera de Paris, Paris, France), 1951 June 1 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1979 March 24 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1979 August 7 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1982 April 10 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 October 29 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1989 November 12 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1993 January 14 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1994 November 26 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1995 April 15 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1999 November 6 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2001 June 29 (Box 2)
- Lucia di Lammermoor (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2002 June 22 (Box 2)
- Luisa Miller (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 December 9 (Box 2)
- Luisa Miller (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 January 30 (Box 2)
- Luisa Miller (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1988 February 13 (Box 2)
- Luisa Miller (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1991 February 23 (Box 2)
- Luisa Miller (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1995 November 12 (Box 2)
- Luisa Miller (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 2000 May 26 (Box 2)
- Luisa Miller (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2000 September 22 (Box 2)
- Luisa Miller (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 November 3 (Box 2)
- Lulu (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1979 August 9 (Box 2)
- Lulu (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1980 December 20 (Box 2)
- Lulu (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 April 6 (Box 2)
- Lulu (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1988 March 25 (Box 2)
- Lulu (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1989 September 23 (Box 2)
- Lulu (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1998 June 28 (Box 2)
- Lulu (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 April 9 (Box 2)
- Lulu Noire (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1997 May 26 (Box 2)
- Luyala (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 2000 March 31 (Box 2)
- Luyala (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 2000 April 1 (Box 2)
- Macbeth (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 December 10 (Box 2)
- Macbeth (Los Angeles Music Center Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1987 December 21 (Box 2)
- Macbeth (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1988 January 30 (Box 2)
- Macbeth (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1994 September 20 (Box 2)
- Macbeth (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1997 October 28 (Box 2)
- Macbeth (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1997 November 7 (Box 2)
- Macbeth (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1998 January 24 (Box 2)
- Macbeth (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1999 December 14 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Royal Opera House, London, England), 1964 December 29 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Operan Stockholm, Stockholm, Sweden), 1966 August 23 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1977 November 26 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (The Goldovsky Opera Theatre, Durham, NC), 1981 February 10 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1983 May 2 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1984 June 23 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (DAC Triangle Music Theater Associates, Durham, NC), 1987 June 9 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1987 August 6 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1987 November 14 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 April 22 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1989 December 9 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1992 June 20 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1994 March 5 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 April 15 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1995 October 17 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1996 July 4 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1997 June 21 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Glimmerglass Opera, Cooperstown, NY), 1997 August 21 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1998 February 13 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1998 July 3 (Box 2)
- Madama Butterfly (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2001 October 27 (Box 2)
- Il Maestro di Cappella (Festival International d'Art Lyrique, Aix-en-Provence, France), 1977 July 21 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (The National Opera Company, Durham, NC), 1976 January 30 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1979 August 10 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1980 August 9 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 January 30 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1981 November 18 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (Volksoper, Vienna, Austria), 1983 December 22 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1984 June 24 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1986 August 6 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (DAC Triangle Music Theater Associates, Durham, NC), 1988 June 7 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1991 January 25 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1991 October 19 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1993 July 10 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1993 August 16 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1993 October 22 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1996 December 14 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1997 May 3 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1997 October 12 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1998 February 5 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (L.A. Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1998 February 19 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1998 July 4 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (UNC-CH Opera Theater Workshop, Chapel Hill, NC), 2000 April 19 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2000 December 6 (Box 2)
- The Magic Flute (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2002 June 22 (Box 2)
- The Makropulos Case (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1981 April 19 (Box 2)
- The Makropulos Case (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1993 October 27 (Box 2)
- The Makropulos Case (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1995 December 13 (Box 2)
- The Makropulos Case (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1996 January 20 (Box 2)
- The Makropulos Case (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1996 February 1 (Box 2)
- The Makropulos Case (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 April 23 (Box 2)
- Les Mamelles de Tiresias (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 March 13 (Box 2)
- Les Mamelles de Tiresias (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 December 11 (Box 2)
- Les Mamelles de Tiresias (UNC-CH Opera Theater Workshop, Chapel Hill, NC), 1992 April 14 (Box 2)
- Les Mamelles de Tiresias (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2002 March 16 (Box 2)
- Manon (Metropolitan Opera, Baltimore, MD), 1955 March 29 (Box 2)
- Manon (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1981 September 18 (Box 2)
- Manon (Staatsoper, Vienna, Austria), 1983 December 21 (Box 2)
- Manon (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 March 7 (Box 2)
- Manon (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 September 19 (Box 2)
- Manon (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1991 February 28 (Box 2)
- Manon (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1997 October 11 (Box 2)
- Manon (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1998 October 20 (Box 2)
- Manon Lescaut (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1980 March 29 (Box 2)
- Manon Lescaut (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1983 November 25 (Box 2)
- Manon Lescaut (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1984 November 3 (Box 2)
- Manon Lescaut (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 October 3 (Box 2)
- Manon Lescaut (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1990 March 10 (Box 2)
- Manon Lescaut (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1998 January 16 (Box 2)
- Manon Lescaut (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 2001 May 25 (Box 2)
- Marco Polo (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1997 November 8 (Box 2)
- Maria Golovin (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1991 May 23 (Box 2)
- Marilyn (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1993 October 9 (Box 2)
- Martha (The National Opera Company and The Dept. of Music, Duke University, Durham, NC), 1978 July 2 (Box 2)
- I Masnadieri (San Diego Civic Theatre, San Diego, CA), 1984 June 30 (Box 2)
- Mathis der Maler (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1995 September 15 (Box 2)
- Mazeppa (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1998 May 7 (Box 2)
- McTeague (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1992 November 9 (Box 2)
- Medea (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1982 April 24 (Box 2)
- The Medium (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1979 May 28 (Box 2)
- The Medium (Winterfest of Contemporary Arts, Durham, NC), 1985 January 11 (Box 2)
- The Medium (Norfolk Center Theatre, Norfolk, VA), 1992 January 24 (Box 2)
- Mefistofele (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1986 October 19 (Box 2)
- Mefistofele (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1989 September 22 (Box 2)
- Mefistofele (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1994 November 27 (Box 2)
- Mefistofele (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1996 March 13 (Box 2)
- Mefistofele (English National Opera, London, England), 1999 April 3 (Box 2)
- Mefistofele (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1999 April 30 (Box 2)
- Mefistofele (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2000 February 26 (Box 2)
- Die Meistersinger von Nurnberg (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1981 July 13 (Box 2)
- Die Meistersinger von Nurnberg (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 March 6 (Box 2)
- Die Meistersinger von Nurnberg (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1985 November 29 (Box 2)
- Die Meistersinger von Nurnberg (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1993 February 6 (Box 2)
- Die Meistersinger von Nurnberg (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1993 October 28 (Box 2)
- Die Meistersinger von Nurnberg (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1998 April 6 (Box 2)
- Die Meistersinger von Nurnberg (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1999 February 24 (Box 2)
- Die Meistersinger von Nurnberg (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2001 October 10 (Box 2)
- The Merchant and the Pauper (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1999 June 25 (Box 2)
- The Merry Widow (Sadler's Wells Opera, London, England), 1958 December 30 (Box 2)
- The Merry Widow (Bayerisches Staatstheater am Gartnerplatz, Munich, Germany), 1977 July 16 (Box 2)
- The Merry Widow (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1981 October 16 (Box 2)
- The Merry Widow (The Eastern Opera Theatre of New York, New York, NY), 1981 November 8 (Box 2)
- The Merry Widow (Theatre Musical de Paris, Paris, France), 1982 December 21 (Box 2)
- The Merry Widow (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1984 May 25 (Box 2)
- The Merry Widow (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1989 June 22 (Box 2)
- The Merry Widow (Opera National de Paris, Paris, France), 1998 November 25 (Box 2)
- The Merry Widow (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2000 February 25 (Box 2)
- The Merry Widow (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2001 December 2 (Box 2)
- The Merry Wives of Windsor (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1990 January 26 (Box 2)
- Les Mesdames de la Halle (Opera Comique, Paris, France), 1983 December 31 (Box 2)
- The Midnight Angel (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1993 June 17 (Box 2)
- The Midsummer Marriage (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1993 October 2 (Box 2)
- A Midsummer Night's Dream (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1992 June 19 (Box 2)
- A Midsummer Night's Dream (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1992 December 10 (Box 2)
- A Midsummer Night's Dream (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1996 January 18 (Box 2)
- A Midsummer Night's Dream (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1996 December 5 (Box 2)
- Mignon (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1982 August 11 (Box 2)
- The Mikado (John F. Kennedy Center, Washington, DC), 1987 March 29 (Box 2)
- The Mikado (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1996 April 12 (Box 2)
- The Miraculous Staircase (Opera Southwest, Albuquerque, NM), 1996 July 19 (Box 2)
- Miss Havisham's Fire (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1979 March 25 (Box 2)
- Miss Havisham's Fire (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2001 June 21 (Box 2)
- Mitridate re di Ponto (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1991 June 22 (Box 2)
- Mitridate re di Ponto (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2001 July 14 (Box 2)
- Modern Painters (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1995 July 29 (Box 2)
- Modern Painters (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1995 August 11 (Box 2)
- Monsieur Choufleuri Restera Chez Lui Le… (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1980 May 28 (Box 2)
- Monsieur Choufleuri Restera Chez Lui Le… (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1981 May 24 (Box 2)
- Monsieur Choufleuri Restera Chez Lui Le… (Opera Comique, Paris, France), 1983 December 31 (Box 2)
- Monsters of Grace (Memorial Hall, Chapel Hill, NC), 1999 January 30 (Box 2)
- Moses und Aron (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1999 October 1 (Box 2)
- The Mother (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1981 May 26 (Box 2)
- The Mother of the Three Sons (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1992 May 16 (Box 2)
- The Mother of Us All (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2000 March 23 (Box 2)
- Mourning Becomes Electra (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1998 October 18 (Box 2)
- The Music Shop (Ava Opera Theatre, Philadelphia, PA), 1997 April 29 (Box 2)
- Nabucco (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1981 June 21 (Box 2)
- Nabucco (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1982 June 17 (Box 2)
- Nabucco (Volksoper, Vienna, Austria), 1993 April 8 (Box 2)
- Nabucco (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1997 October 4 (Box 2)
- Nabucco (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1999 December 3 (Box 2)
- Nabucco (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 2000 April 29 (Box 2)
- Nixon in China (Brooklyn Academy of Music, Brooklyn, NY), 1987 December 4 (Box 2)
- Norma (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 April 13 (Box 2)
- Norma (Staatsoper, Vienna, Austria), 1980 June 18 (Box 2)
- Norma (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 September 25 (Box 2)
- Norma (L.A. Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1996 September 15 (Box 2)
- Norma (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1997 February 6 (Box 2)
- Norma (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1998 November 18 (Box 2)
- Norma (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 October 19 (Box 2)
- The Nose (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1987 August 1 (Box 2)
- The Nose (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1987 August 5 (Box 2)
- Now Eleanor's Idea (SITE Santa Fe, Santa Fe, NM), 1995 August 6 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 0200 July 1 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1977 March 10 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Bayerische Staatsoper Nationaltheater Munchen, Munich, Germany), 1977 July 14 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1982 August 10 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1982 October 15 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (The Royal Opera, London, England), 1982 December 31 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1985 August 1 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 December 7 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1986 September 12 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1987 August 4 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1988 December 24 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1989 May 29 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1990 June 9 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1990 June 23 (Box 2)